<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:cc="http://web.resource.org/cc/" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#">
    <channel>
        <title>The Ally Tour Podcast</title>
        <link>http://tour.ally.ac</link>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <copyright>&#xA9;2018 Blackboard Ally</copyright>
        <webMaster>your@email.com (Your Name)</webMaster>
        <managingEditor>info@ally.ac (Blackboard Ally)</managingEditor>
        <image>
            <url>http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/assets/img/2019-tour-podcast-cover-art.png</url>
            <title>2019 Ally Tour Cover Art</title>
            <link>http://tour.ally.ac</link>
        </image>
        <itunes:owner>
            <itunes:name>Blackboard Ally</itunes:name>
            <itunes:email>info@ally.ac</itunes:email>
        </itunes:owner>
        <itunes:category text="Education"></itunes:category>
        <itunes:category text="Higher Education"></itunes:category>
        <itunes:keywords>accessibility,a11y,coursecontent,universaldesignforlearning,udl,remediation</itunes:keywords>
        <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
        <itunes:image href="http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/assets/img/2019-tour-podcast-cover-art.png" />
        <atom:link href="http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/allytour-feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        <title>The Ally Tour Podcast</title>
        <itunes:author>Blackboard Ally</itunes:author>
        <description>We're on a worldwide search to see what inclusive education looks like in the digital age. So Blackboard Ally is going on Tour, visiting campuses around the globe to learn how they're tackling their toughest accessibility challenges and improving the learning experience for all students.</description>
        <itunes:summary>We're on a worldwide search to see what inclusive education looks like in the digital age. So Blackboard Ally is going on Tour, visiting campuses around the globe to learn how they're tackling their toughest accessibility challenges and improving the learning experience for all students.</itunes:summary>
        <itunes:subtitle>What does inclusive education looks like in our modern age? Blackboard Ally is visiting campuses around the globe to learn how they're tackling their toughest accessibility challenges and improving the learning experience for all students.</itunes:subtitle>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 09:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <!-- TRAILER-->
        <item>
            <itunes:episodeType>trailer</itunes:episodeType>
            <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
            <title>Introducing the Ally Tour for 2019</title>
            <description>The 2019 Ally Tour Trailer is an overview of our plans to visit as many institutions around the globe as possible for 2019. It includes some of the activities we are planning carrying out and how to follow the tour. Join the tour along with the rest of the Ally Community at tour.ally.ac. You can catch the latest updates on Instagram and Twitter at #AllyTour2019. And listen to stories of inclusion from our Community Champions on the Ally Tour 2019 Podcast series available on SoundCloud or in your favorite podcast app. We’ll look forward to seeing you at the next stop on the road to IncluCity.</description>
            <itunes:summary>The 2019 Ally Tour Trailer is an overview of our plans to visit as many institutions around the globe as possible for 2019. It includes some of the activities we are planning carrying out and how to follow the tour.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:subtitle>The 2019 Ally Tour Trailer is an overview of our plans to visit as many institutions around the globe as possible for 2019. It includes some of the activities we are planning carrying out and how to follow the tour.</itunes:subtitle>
            <enclosure url="http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/2019-ally-tour-trailer.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="1690088" />
            <guid>http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/2019-ally-tour-trailer.mp3</guid>
            <link>https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/custom_pages/container/view?id=36</link>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:author>Blackboard Ally</itunes:author>
            <itunes:duration>00:01:10</itunes:duration>
            <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <!--END TRAILER-->
        <!-- EPISODE 01-->
        <item>
            <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
            <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
            <title>Ep01: Atlantic Cape Community College – Rising up to the Challenge</title>
            <itunes:title>Atlantic Cape Community College – Rising up to the Challenge: A Three-Year Journey to a more Inclusive Campus</itunes:title>
            <description>After receiving a complaint from the Office of Civil Rights, a Community College faces the tall task of becoming accessible in three years. How did they respond in the face of adversity? In the first episode of the Ally Tour, we hear from the team at Atlantic Cape Community College in New Jersey their journey on the pathway to inclusion. Now three years later, inclusivity has become a core part of their campus culture. Their story is an inspiration for the many institutions out there facing similar challenges in becoming more inclusive, and a lesson about how in the end, it really is about student success.</description>
            <itunes:summary>After receiving a complaint from the Office of Civil Rights, a Community College faces the tall task of becoming accessible in three years. How did they respond in the face of adversity? In the first episode of the Ally Tour, we hear from the team at Atlantic Cape Community College in New Jersey their journey on the pathway to inclusion. Now three years later, inclusivity has become a core part of their campus culture. Their story is an inspiration for the many institutions out there facing similar challenges in becoming more inclusive, and a lesson about how in the end, it really is about student success.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:subtitle>A Community College makes a campus-wide commitment to accessibility to create more equitable, higher quality learning experiences for students.</itunes:subtitle>
            <enclosure url="http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/ep01-atlantic-cape.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="75196095" />
            <guid>http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/ep01-atlantic-cape.mp3</guid>
            <link><![CDATA[https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/custom_pages/container/view?id=36]]></link>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:author>Blackboard Ally</itunes:author>
            <itunes:duration>00:56:38</itunes:duration>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Feb 2019 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                <p>For the first stop on the Ally Tour, John Scott of the Ally Team visits <a href="http://www.atlantic.edu">Atlantic Cape Community College</a> in New Jersey. Members of the Instructional Technology group and the Center for Accessibility sit down to share their story.</p>
                <p>After two blind students and the National Federation for the Blind filed a lawsuit against the campus for failing to provide equitable access to their learning content for students with disabilities, the team was issued a <a href="http://www.atlantic.edu/documents/nfb_lanzailotti_atlantic_cape_consent_decree.pdf">Consent Decree</a> to become 100% accessible in three years.</p>
                <p>In the beginning, the team talks about when they first heard about the decree, and where they and their faculty were in terms of accessibility at that time. They then share go into detail about the processes they put into place and strategies they developed to begin the long march toward inclusion.</p>
                <p>Part of that process included becoming an early adopted of Blackboard Ally, which became a crucial tool for them in monitoring their progress and training faculty. So where are they today? </p>
                <p>In the end, the team discusses how they have witnessed a culture change on their campus, where faculty haven’t only prioritized accessibility in their teaching for the sake of compliance, but because they have found a more inclusive campus benefits all their learners.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Michelle Perkins – Director of Instructional Technology</li>
                    <li>Chad Bullock – Senior Manager Adaptive Technology</li>
                    <li>Mike Barnes – Director of the Center for Accessibility</li>
                    <li>Joshua Carroll – Senior Technician Instructional Technology</li>
                    <li>Patricia Kubaska – Program Coordinator Instructional Technology</li>
                    <li>Gerald Fox – Faculty Support</li>
                </ul>
                <p><a href="http://www.atlantic.edu">www.atlantic.edu</a></p>
                <br/>
                <p>The Ally Tour Blog:<a href="https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/custom_pages/container/view?id=36">http://tour.ally.ac</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BbAllyTour2019?src=hash" title="Twitter Searching #BbAllyTour2109" target="_blank">#AllyTour2019</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BbAlly?src=hash" title="Twitter Searching #BbAlly" target="_blank">#BbAlly on Twitter</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/ally_tour_2019/" title="@Ally_Tour_2019 on Instagram" target="_blank">@Ally_Tour_2019 on Instagram</a></p>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <itunes:keywords>ada504,rehabilitationact,communitycollege,wcag,accessible,atlanticcapecommunitycollege,accc,ally,blackboardally,inclusive,accessibility,a11y,coursecontent,universaldesignforlearning,udl,studentremediation,studentsupport,studentservices</itunes:keywords>
        </item>
        <!--END EPISODE 01-->
        <!-- EPISODE 02-->
        <item>
            <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
            <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
            <title>Ep02: Lesley University - Technology for Social Justice</title>
            <itunes:title>Lesley University - Technology for Social Justice</itunes:title>
            <description>In this second episode of the Ally Tour, we speak with the team at Lesley University and how they’ve experienced their inclusivity journey. Built on the core principle of social justice, Lesley University truly embraces an accessibility and inclusivity mindset. About 3 years ago, the school’s general counsel office embarked on a mission on how to be more proactive with making digital content more accessible. Since then, the team has rolled out various accessibility initiatives successfully and Ally helped them do this in a more streamlined and holistic way.</description>
            <itunes:summary>In this second episode of the Ally Tour, we speak with the team at Lesley University and how they’ve experienced their inclusivity journey. Built on the core principle of social justice, Lesley University truly embraces an accessibility and inclusivity mindset. About 3 years ago, the school’s general counsel office embarked on a mission on how to be more proactive with making digital content more accessible. Since then, the team has rolled out various accessibility initiatives successfully and Ally helped them do this in a more streamlined and holistic way.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:subtitle>A Tradition of Supporting Equity and Access in Education</itunes:subtitle>
            <enclosure url="http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/ep02-lesley.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="59565593" />
            <guid>http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/ep02-lesley.mp3</guid>
            <link><![CDATA[https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/blog/view?id=57]]></link>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:author>Blackboard Ally</itunes:author>
            <itunes:duration>00:41:21</itunes:duration>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                <p>For the second stop on the Ally Tour, John Scott of the Ally Team visits Lesley University in Cambridge, Massachusetts. The team shares its passion for Social Justice, and how accessibility and Universal Design for Learning have always been an important topic on campus.</p>
                <p>In the beginning, the team talks about how the school’s general counsel office embarked on a mission on how to be more proactive with making digital content more accessible.</p>
                <p>With the efforts that came from the counsel office and the important support from leadership, Lesley University also benefited from having Ally in making it more accessible and supporting that concerted view.</p>
                <p>The discussion moves on to talking about how they secured funding, their overall (very quick!) roll-out of Ally, how they trained their faculty and how students perceived the Alternative Formats.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Robyn Belair - Instructional Technologist</li>
                    <li>Kristina McElroy - Director of Academic Technology</li>
                    <li>Danielle Powell - Instructional Technologist</li>
                    <li>Heather Tillberg Web - Associate Provost, Systems, Planning & Administration</li>
                </ul>
                <p><a href="http://www.lesley.edu">www.lesley.edu</a></p>
                <br/>
                <p>The Ally Tour Blog:<a href="https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/custom_pages/container/view?id=36">http://tour.ally.ac</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BbAllyTour2019?src=hash" title="Twitter Searching #BbAllyTour2109" target="_blank">#AllyTour2019</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BbAlly?src=hash" title="Twitter Searching #BbAlly" target="_blank">#BbAlly on Twitter</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/ally_tour_2019/" title="@Ally_Tour_2019 on Instagram" target="_blank">@Ally_Tour_2019 on Instagram</a></p>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <itunes:keywords>ada504,rehabilitationact,communitycollege,wcag,accessible,lesley,lesleyuniversity,accc,ally,blackboardally,inclusive,accessibility,a11y,coursecontent,universaldesignforlearning,udl,studentremediation,studentsupport,studentservices</itunes:keywords>
        </item>
        <!--END EPISODE 02-->
        <!-- EPISODE 03-->
        <item>
            <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
            <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
            <title>EP03: UC Berkeley - A history of free speech, diversity and accessibility</title>
            <itunes:title>An R1 University’s history of free speech and supporting students with disabilities</itunes:title>
            <description>As the birthplace of the Free Speech Movement, advocacy for minorities and people with disabilities is at the core of UC Berkeley. During the third episode of the Ally Tour, we learn more about Berkeley’s rich history of inclusion and equity, and how accessibility fits into the bigger picture. We hear from Lucy Greco and Joseph Feria-Galicia about their involvement with Ally, and how faculty and students reacted.</description>
            <itunes:summary>As the birthplace of the Free Speech Movement, advocacy for minorities and people with disabilities is at the core of UC Berkeley. During the third episode of the Ally Tour, we learn more about Berkeley’s rich history of inclusion and equity, and how accessibility fits into the bigger picture. We hear from Lucy Greco and Joseph Feria-Galicia about their involvement with Ally, and how faculty and students reacted.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:subtitle>An R1 University’s history of free speech and supporting students with disabilities</itunes:subtitle>
            <enclosure url="http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/ep03-ucberkeley.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="68553103" />
            <guid>http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/ep03-ucberkeley.mp3</guid>
            <link><![CDATA[https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/custom_pages/view?id=55]]></link>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:author>Blackboard Ally</itunes:author>
            <itunes:duration>00:47:36</itunes:duration>
            <pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                <p>The third stop on the Ally Tour brings us to UC Berkeley in California, where we’re fortunate to talk to accessibility champion and Paralympics Bronze medal winner Lucy Greco and Accessibility Team Lead, Joseph Feria-Galicia. As the birthplace of the Free Speech Movement, advocacy for minorities and people with disabilities is at the core of UC Berkeley.</p>
                <p>During the first half of the podcast, Lucy talks about Berkeley’s history of free speech, and the community of students with disabilities pushing for a more accessible learning experience in the 60’s. She continues the conversation about the relationship and difference between accessibility and UDL, and the challenges faculty face when tools are often limited in terms of accessibility. She highlights how it’s important to continue to engage with faculty.</p>
                <p>During the second part of the podcast, Joseph talks about his involvement and the roll-out strategy of Ally, and how it helped bring a culture change across campus. We hear about the reactions from both faculty and students, and how the team plans to continue their efforts on creating an accessible environment for all students.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Lucy Greco - Assistive Technologist Specialist and Accessibility Evangelist, UC Berkeley</li>
                    <li>Joseph Feria-Galicia - Accessibility Team Lead, UC Berkeley </li>
                </ul>
                <p><a href="http://www.berkeley.edu">www.berkeley.edu</a></p>
                <br/>
                <p>The Ally Tour Blog:<a href="https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/custom_pages/container/view?id=36">http://tour.ally.ac</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BbAllyTour2019?src=hash" title="Twitter Searching #BbAllyTour2109" target="_blank">#AllyTour2019</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BbAlly?src=hash" title="Twitter Searching #BbAlly" target="_blank">#BbAlly on Twitter</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/ally_tour_2019/" title="@Ally_Tour_2019 on Instagram" target="_blank">@Ally_Tour_2019 on Instagram</a></p>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <itunes:keywords>accessibility,accessible,bbally,ally,blackboardally,inclusive,coursecontent,universaldesignforlearning,udl,UCBerkeley,freespeech</itunes:keywords>
        </item>
        <!--END EPISODE 03-->
        <!-- EPISODE 04-->
        <item>
            <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
            <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
            <title>EP04: Gaston College – When serendipitous encounters lead to success</title>
            <itunes:title>Serendipitous encounters leading to great success</itunes:title>
            <description>During the fourth episode of the Ally Tour, we learn from the team at Gaston College, North Carolina, how a serendipitous encounter at a conference turned into a success story of bringing accessibility and inclusiveness to their college. We hear from Karen Duncan and Kim Gelsinger how the importance of working with deans, building a great team and making sure processes are in place, allows for all students to be able to navigate their courses successfully.</description>
            <itunes:summary>During the fourth episode of the Ally Tour, we learn from the team at Gaston College, North Carolina, how a serendipitous encounter at a conference turned into a success story of bringing accessibility and inclusiveness to their college. We hear from Karen Duncan and Kim Gelsinger how the importance of working with deans, building a great team and making sure processes are in place, allows for all students to be able to navigate their courses successfully.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:subtitle>Serendipitous encounters leading to great success</itunes:subtitle>
            <enclosure url="http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/ep04-gaston-college.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="62640532" />
            <guid>http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/ep04-gaston-college.mp3</guid>
            <link><![CDATA[https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/custom_pages/view?id=55]]></link>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:author>Blackboard Ally</itunes:author>
            <itunes:duration>00:43:29</itunes:duration>
            <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2019 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                <p>The fourth stop on the Ally tour brings us to Gaston College in North Carolina, where we’re excited to meet with Kim Gelsinger and Karen Duncan and hear what their strategies have been to become a more inclusive campus.</p>
                <p>In the beginning, the team talks about an online quality initiative which had been running since 2007 but it had been challenging to get an overall sense of where they were at in terms of accessibility.</p>
                <p>The team was very excited when first hearing about Blackboard Ally at a conference, which quickly followed by a smooth roll-out and pilots. Thanks to the support of their deans and the help from their team, Gaston College has been able to develop an efficient process where they utilize Ally’s Institutional Report to support their accessibility efforts.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Karen Duncan - Instructional Technology Specialist </li>
                    <li>Kim Gelsinger - Director of Distance Education  </li>
                </ul>
                <p><a href="https://www.gaston.edu/">www.gaston.edu/</a></p>
                <br/>
                <p>The Ally Tour Blog:<a href="https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/custom_pages/container/view?id=36">http://tour.ally.ac</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BbAllyTour2019?src=hash" title="Twitter Searching #BbAllyTour2109" target="_blank">#AllyTour2019</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BbAlly?src=hash" title="Twitter Searching #BbAlly" target="_blank">#BbAlly on Twitter</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/ally_tour_2019/" title="@Ally_Tour_2019 on Instagram" target="_blank">@Ally_Tour_2019 on Instagram</a></p>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <itunes:keywords>accessibility,accessible,bbally,ally,blackboardally,inclusive,a11y,universaldesignforlearning,udl,GastonCollege</itunes:keywords>
        </item>
        <!--END EPISODE 04-->
        <!-- EPISODE 05-->
        <item>
            <itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType>
            <itunes:season>1</itunes:season>
            <title>EP05: MUSC - Tackling unique challenges at a Medical university</title>
            <itunes:title>How a medical university approaches their unique accessibility challenges</itunes:title>
            <description>As a University as well as a hospital, the Medical University of South Carolina doesn’t only look after its students but also its many patients. During this fifth episode, we learn how a medical University faces some unique accessibility challenges, ranging from complex medical images, to linking to medical journal articles. We hear from Melissa Hortman and Alex Walters how MUSC approached this and how liaising with key stakeholders such as librarians, as well as using Ally’s ‘hidden gem’ feature the Library Reference, helped contribute towards a successful accessibility journey.</description>
            <itunes:summary>As a University as well as a hospital, the Medical University of South Carolina doesn’t only look after its students but also its many patients. During this fifth episode, we learn how a medical University faces some unique accessibility challenges, ranging from complex medical images, to linking to medical journal articles. We hear from Melissa Hortman and Alex Walters how MUSC approached this and how liaising with key stakeholders such as librarians, as well as using Ally’s ‘hidden gem’ feature the Library Reference, helped contribute towards a successful accessibility journey.</itunes:summary>
            <itunes:subtitle>How a medical university approaches their unique accessibility challenges</itunes:subtitle>
            <enclosure url="http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/ep04-gaston-college.mp3" type="audio/mpeg" length="64905528" />
            <guid>http://www.ally.ac/podcast/tour/ep05-musc.mp3</guid>
            <link><![CDATA[https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/custom_pages/view?id=55]]></link>
            <itunes:explicit>no</itunes:explicit>
            <itunes:author>Blackboard Ally</itunes:author>
            <itunes:duration>00:45:04</itunes:duration>
            <pubDate>Mon, 01 July 2019 09:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[
                <p>As a University as well as a hospital, the Medical University of South Carolina doesn’t only look after its students but also its many patients.</p>
                During this fifth episode, we learn how a medical University faces some unique accessibility challenges, ranging from complex medical images, to linking to medical journal articles.</p>
                <p>We hear from Melissa Hortman and Alex Walters how MUSC approached this and how liaising with key stakeholders such as librarians, as well as using Ally’s ‘hidden gem’ feature the Library Reference, helped contribute towards a successful accessibility journey.</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Melissa Hortman Ed.D. - Assistant Professor, Director of Instructional Technology</li>
                    <li>Alex Walters - Senior Instructional Designer and Digital Accessibility Specialist</li>
                </ul>
                <p><a href="https://web.musc.edu/">web.musc.edu</a></p>
                <br/>
                <p>The Ally Tour Blog:<a href="https://usergroup.ally.ac/s/tour/custom_pages/container/view?id=36">http://tour.ally.ac</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BbAllyTour2019?src=hash" title="Twitter Searching #BbAllyTour2109" target="_blank">#AllyTour2019</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/BbAlly?src=hash" title="Twitter Searching #BbAlly" target="_blank">#BbAlly on Twitter</a></p>
                <p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/ally_tour_2019/" title="@Ally_Tour_2019 on Instagram" target="_blank">@Ally_Tour_2019 on Instagram</a></p>
                ]]>
            </content:encoded>
            <itunes:keywords>musc,medicaluniversityofsouthcarolina,accessibility,accessible,bbally,ally,blackboardally,inclusive,a11y,universaldesignforlearning,udl</itunes:keywords>
        </item>
        <!--END EPISODE 05-->
    </channel>
</rss>
